var questionlist = [
  {
    question: "",
    answer:["", "", "", ""],
    correctAns:0

  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer:["", "", "", ""],
    correctAns:1

  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer:["", "", "", ""],
    correctAns:3

  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer:["", "", "", ""],
    correctAns:3

  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer:["", "", "", ""],
    correctAns:3

  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer:["", "", "", ""],
    correctAns:1

  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer:["", "", "", ""],
    correctAns:1

  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer:["", "", "", ""],
    correctAns:2

  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer:["", "", "", ""],
    correctAns:2

  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer:["", "", "", ""],
    correctAns:3

  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer:["", "", "", ""],
    correctAns:2

  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer:["", "", "", ""],
    correctAns:1

  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer:["", "", "", ""],
    correctAns:0

  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer:["", "", "", ""],
    correctAns:2

  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer:["", "", "", ""],
    correctAns:0

  },
]

var begingingEl = document.getElementById("beginPage");
var questionCardEl = document.getElementById("questionCard");
var questionsEl = document.getElementById("question");
var answersEl = document.getElementById("answerCard");
var timerEl = document.getElementById("timer");

var beginBtn = document.getElementById("beginBtn");
var signBtn = document.querySelector("#sign");
var returnBtn = document.querySelector("#return")
 
